Welcome back to Abhi Want To Table Job YouTube
channel, I am Ishant Sharma and in today's
video I am going to tell you about
ICICI Lombard's new job
opening and Unit Sales Manager.
In this video we are going to discuss what
your job role will be, interview questions you
can ask everyone, what will be your eligibility criteria,
how can you apply for the job,
which job location
is available, then we will see what salary you can get,
so you will see the end of this video,
I am going to tell you all this and
if you want us to make a video on any other job
profile then please let us
know by writing in the comment section and friends,
if you want to do any customer or serial solid
job interview for that
then you can download Job Step from Google Play Store,
I have
given the link in the description, so let's
start this video, so friends,
ICICI Lombard is an insurance company,
here you can see many types of their insurance
accounts, travel insurance,
showroom, two wheeler insurance, home
insurance, health insurance, there are many of
their product services, now what about
you  The job role will be like
Unit Sales Manager at ICICI
Lombard. Your role will be to recruit
and train new sales agents. You will be
telling them how to increase your sales, how to
send SMS to more and more products
of ICICI Lombard.
You will be explaining to them all the policies of ICICI Lombard, insurance policies.
After that, you will maintain clear
relationships with the employees
and you will be explaining to them about all the products and services.
And this is a
target based role. This means that you will have to
achieve some target charges.
Now friends, let's see what location the
job is available in. If you
recruit in many locations, you can see it
here in Bangalore, Hyderabad, Bhadra,
Nagpur and Chandigarh also. So,
request from all these job locations like
grading. Now let's see what eligibility
criteria are required, what
qualifications you should have. If
you want to apply for this job, then
you should be selected
in any specialization.  This is hummus, you should have some
experience in it, this
is mandatory, after that you should have good
communication skills, this is very
important because you will be training the apps,
managing them, planning them, and
explaining things to the planets, so keep making it, so this is very
important to have, now let's see
what salary you can expect, you can get
from one like
55125 last fifty thousand abscond, in this
I told you this target send roller,
in this you also get additional incentives
as you achieve these targets,
now friends let's see what interview
questions we can ask, so
basically in this interview questions can be candy
crush number one type questions, so
how well can you express yourself, we
can ask you about your s&p communication ability, tell us about yourself,
what is your office, your short term and
What are your long term goals? Then you can ask us
why you resigned from your previous company
or you can ask that question.
So understand your knowledge about
general insurance. This question can be asked to you.
What is PM post sales according to you?
What are the qualities of a good sales manager?
Then you can ask some questions to understand
how you will react in any situation.
One of the situations can be if
a client comes to you who is very upset with
ICICI Lombard's products and
services, then how will you handle him?
How will you deal with him? Friends,
if you want to know how to answer these questions,
then you
can simply download Jobsapp from Google Play Store. I have
given the link in the description. So
friends, now let's see how you have to apply for this role. So friends, to
apply, go to
Naukri.com website.
This is a job search
platform for jobs. After coming here, you have to
search in the search box. Here
you  You will write Unit Sales
Manager ICICI Lombard by writing
that you can search and here you
can see, after installing here you have
changed the experience to Tube
Burners
and after that you can see here
all the job locations where they are recruiting,
so here there is Bangalore, Ludhiana,
Chandigarh also, Hyderabad, so it
is available in many job locations,
if you want to apply for this, then
I will show you Bhangarh, the procedure will be the
same for all the others,
click on it, then here it will give you the
description of the entire job opening, the
size will tell you about it,
click here to apply, this is applicable on the
condition, here you will also have to
create your account on sacrifice naukri.com, here you will have to
enter your basic information, you will have to
put your resume and in this way you
can apply for the job and friends, the
plan is not written for you job, it is completely
related, it is completely real
Directly ICICI Lombard has
listed it on naukri.com, so you
can definitely apply from here.
Now friends, if you want to prepare
for your interview for Unit Sales Manager
at ICICI Lombard, then you can simply
download Jobsapp from Google Play Store.
But basically,
you can enroll in many free courses and learn
which questions can be asked to you,
how to answer them in the show, how
can you present some and
you can know a lot of information
about yourself, friends, I have
given the link in the description, you
can download it from there. So friends, thank you so much
for watching. If you have any question, then
definitely tell us by clicking on the comment. If
you want us to
make a video on someone else's profile, then
comment in the latest music listening channel. See you in the
next video.